byron.com.au 2019-03-06

# Byron Employment - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Byron Employment's Privacy Policy - Introduction

Byron Employment recognises the importance of protecting the privacy of its users, and it is committed to providing a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains confidential, and is used only for the purposes set out in the following policy.

### Information About All Byron Employment Users

To assist us in monitoring the performance of the site and improving services for users, we routinely gather information about users on a collective basis. This information does not allow us to identify specific users, and the data is only ever use in the aggregate. We may from time to time share this information with our partners, to allow them to evaluate the performance of our service and tailor the content to the requirements of users.

### Information About Specific Users

In some circumstances we may need more specific information about you, such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, job preference etc. When we request such information from you we will generally explain why we require it, or it will be obvious from the context in which you are using our services. From time to time we may contact subscribers to our email service to inform them of changes to the site or to provide information that we believe they will find useful.

### General Information Disclosure

Apart from for the purposes of applying for positions listed on the site or where we believe it is required by law, we will not disclose to third parties information about individual visits to Byron Employment or personal information that you provide. Where information is passed to one of our partner companies as part of the application process, Byron Employment will not be responsible for the usage of the information that the partner company receives.

### Security

Byron Employment takes all reasonable steps ensure the security of user information entrusted to us, and our servers are securely located in a leading edge facility. However, no facility on the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure, and we will not be held responsible for the consequences of unauthorised access of your personal information.

### Feedback

Users are encouraged to submit feedback regarding the Byron Employment service via our website or directly by email. Any feedback that is submitted in this manner becomes the property of Byron Employment, and we reserve the right to use it for marketing purposes in a manner that will preserve your anonymity.

### Privacy Commitment Changes

Should we decide to change the privacy policy outlined above, we will post those changes on the site to ensure you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please email us at [admin@byron.com.au](mailto:admin@byron.com.au)
